Impartial Umpire Files 6057
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Impartial Umpire Files
1934-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
6057
24 cubic feet
24 linear ft.
Records.
This file contains the awards of the umpires in those industries where an impartial umpire system has been established. Auto steel and meat packing are included at present, but others will be added.
5771290
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 30, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 18, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Cases; Iron and steel workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Automobile industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Steel industry and trade -- United States; Bethlehem Steel Company; Chrysler Corporation; Ford Motor Company; General Motors Corporation; United States Steel Corporation
5771290
- General Motors Umpire Decisions. (Box 1)
  - General Motors Code of Umpire Conduct, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - UE General Motors Digest of Umpire Decisions, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions A, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions C, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions D, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions E 1-50, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions E 51 -100, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions E 101-150, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions E 151-200, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions E 201-250, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions E 251-300, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions E 301-350, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions F 1-100, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions F 101-200, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions G, 1951-1956 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions H, 1956-1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions Series J, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions Series K, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions Series L, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions Series M, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions Ad Hoc Cases, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - General Motors Umpire Decisions Special Cases, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Ford Motor Co. Umpire Decisions. (Box 2)
  - Ford Motor Company Umpire Decisions MB 1-50, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Ford Motor Company Umpire Decisions Series SW, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ford Motor Company Umpire Decisions Series RH, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ford Motor Company Umpire Decisions Series HP, 1951-1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Ford Motor Company Umpire Decisions Series DPM, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ford Motor Company Umpire Decisions Series M, 1948-1950 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Ford Motor Company Umpire Decisions Index to Umpire Memorandum, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Ford Motor Company Umpire Decisions A, 1946-1952 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ford Motor Company Umpire Decisions B, 1953-1959 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Ford Motor Company Umpire Decisions Series CK, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Chrysler Corp. Appeal Board Decisions #1-2599. (Box 3)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 100-199, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions- 200-299, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 300-399, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 400-499, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board- Decisions- 500-599, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board- Decisions 600-699, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board- Decisions 700-799, 1949-1951 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board- Decisions 800-899, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 900-999, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 1000-1099, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 1100-1199, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 1200-1299, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 1300-1399, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 1400-1499, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board- Decisions 1500-1599, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board- Decisions 1600-1699, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 1700-1799, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 1800-1899, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 1900-1999 ( Catalog Annually), 1957 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 2000-2099, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board- Decisions 2100-2199, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 2200-2599, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Chrysler Corp. Appeal Board Decisions 2600-3999, E-1-E-289, 0-1-0-1300, p.22, Salaried Umpire Digest. (Box 4)
  - Digest of Umpire Decisions (Chrysler - UAW) for Use of Bargaining Representative, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Decisions from 1943 to June 1, 1958
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board- Decisions 2600-2999, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board- Decisions 3000-3999, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions E-1 -, 1947-1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board- Decisions 0-1 - 0-99, 1948-1952 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 0-100 - 0-199, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 0-200 - 0-299, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 0-300 - 0-399, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 0-400 - 0-499, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 0-500 - 0-599, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board - Decisions 0-600 - 0-1300, 1954-1960 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Chrysler Corporation Appeal Board Decisions P-22, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Chrysler Salaried Umpire Digest, 1947-1960 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Chemical & Allied Products Industry (National Lead Co.), Meat Packing Industry Arbitration Awards. (Box 5)
  - Chemical & Allied Products Industry National Lead Company, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Chemical and Allied Products Industry- National Lead Company, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Armour and Company Arbitration Awards Series CK, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Armour and Company Arbitration Awards Series HB, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Armour and Company Arbitration Awards Series (C?)- G, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Armour and Company Grievances, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 37 Cuday Packing Company Arbitration Awards, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - EMGE and Sons Arbitration Awards, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - John Morrell and Company Arbitration Awards, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Kuhner Packing Company Arbitration Awards, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Libby, McNeill and Libby Arbitration Awards, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - National Food Stores, Inc. Arbitration Awards, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - The Schmadel Packing Company Arbitration Awards, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Swift and Company Arbitration Awards, 1946-1948 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Swift and Company Arbitration Awards, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Wilson and Company Arbitration Awards, 1945-1948 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- American Newspaper Guild Arbitration Reports 1958-1967. (Box 6)
  - American Newspaper Guild Index to Arbitration Reports, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - American Newspaper Guild 1958 Arbitration Reports (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - American Newspaper Guild 1959 Arbitration Reports (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - American Newspaper Guild 1960 Arbitration Reports (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - American Newspaper Guild 1961 Arbitration Reports (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - American Newspaper Guild 1962 Arbitration Reports (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - American Newspaper Guild 1963 Arbitration Reports (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - American Newspaper Guild 1964 Arbitration Reports (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - American Newspaper Guild 1964 Arbitration Reports (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - American Newspaper Guild 1965 Arbitration Reports (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - American Newspaper Guild 1966 Arbitration Reports (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Misc. Arbitration Reports - 1967 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Bethlehem Steel Co. Umpire Decisions # 1-550. (Box 7)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Impartial Umpire - Decisions 1-49, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Impartial Umpire - Decisions 50-99, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Impartial Umpire * Decisions 100-149, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Impartial Umpire - Decisions 150-199, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Impartial Umpire- Decisions 200-249, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Impartial Umpire- Decisions 250-299, 1955-1957 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Impartial Umpire - Decisions 300-349, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Impartial Umpire 350-400, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company- Impartial Umpire Decisions # 451-499, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions # 400-450, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions # 500-550, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Bethlehem Steel Co. Umpire Decisions # 551-1299. (Box 8)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions # 551-599, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions # 600-650, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions # 651-699, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions # 700-799, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions #800-850, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions # 851-899, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions #900-999, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions #100-1050, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions #1051-1099, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions # 1100 - 1199, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions #1200-1299, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Bethlehem Steel Co. Umpire Decisions # 1300-1999. (Box 9)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions #1300-1399, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions 1400-1499, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions 1500-1599, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1500-1599, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1600-1699, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1700-1799, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1800-1899, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1900-1999, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Bethlehem Steel Co. Umpire Decisions # 2000-3099. (Box 10)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions 2000-2199, 1972-1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 2200-2299, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 2300-2399, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 2400-2499, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 2500-2599, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 2600-2699, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 2700-2799, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 2900-3099, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Bethlehem Steel Co. Umpire Decisions dates 1947-1952. (Box 11)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire - Grievances - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1948 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1948 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances 1949 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1949 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1949 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances -1950 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1950 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1951 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances 1951 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1952 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Bethlehem Steel Co. Umpire Decisions dates 1953-1965, 1972-1983. (Box 12)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1953 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances 1954 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1955 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1956 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1957, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1958 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances 1959 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1960 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- Grievances - 1965, 1980-1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1980 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1980 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1980 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1981 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- 1983 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Bethlehem Steel Co. Miscellaneous Impartial Umpire Decisions. (Box 13)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire- AS # 1-50, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions AS # 51-100, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions COG # 1 - 49, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions FX 1-50, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions- F 1-50, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions DAC 1-50, 1964-1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions GAD # 1-49, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions LGM 1-50, 1964-1968 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions HHP # 1-49, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions PS # 1-49, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Shipbuilding Div.--Staten Island, N.Y. Umpire Decisions 1-, 1958-1960 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Shipbuilding Div. - Quincy Mass. Umpire Decisions 1-, 1948-1959 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Shipbuilding Div.- Quincy, Mass. Umpire Decisions NS 1-, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions S # 1-50, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions S # 51-100, 1957-1960 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions S # 101-150, 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Shipbuilding Div.- Sparrows Point, Md. Umpire Decisions 1-, 1956-1959 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company and American Federation of Technical Engineers, AFL-CIO, 1959-1962 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Shipbuilding Div. - Baltimore, Md. Umpire Decision 1-, 1955-1966 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Shipbuilding Div. - Brooklyn, N.Y. Umpire Decisions 1-, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Shipbuilding Div.- Hoboken, N.J. Umpire Decisions 1-, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Shipbuilding Divisions Umpire Decisions DAC 1-50, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Shipbuilding Division Umpire Decisions ER 1-50, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Shipbuilding Division Umpire Decisions LGM 1-50, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company Shipbuilding Division Umpire Decisions FX 1-50, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Impartial Umpire Decisions Grievance 76-7, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- U.S. Steel Arbitrations HS Series- U.S.C. 1400-1599. (Box 14)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration HS-Series, 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration No. S 1-100, 1963-1965 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration SUB- Series, 1965-1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USC 200-399, 1952-1961 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - United States Steel Corp. Board of Arbitration USC 400-599, 1954-1957 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. - Board of Arbitration USC 600-699, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. - Board of Arbitration USC 700-799, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - United States Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration - USC 1000-1199 (Folder 1 of 2), 1960-1962 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - United States Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration - USC 1000-1199 (Folder 1 of 2), 1960-1962 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - United States Steel Corp. Board of Arbitration USC 800-999, 1959-1962 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - United States Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration - USC 1400-1599, 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - United States Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration - USC 1200-1399, 1962-1966 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- U.S. Steel Arbitrations - U.S.C. 1600-2200, U.S.S. 4800-5299. (Box 15)
  - United States Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration - USC 1600-1799 (Folder 1 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - United States Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration - USC 1600-1799 (Folder 2 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration # USC 1800-1999 (Folder 1 of 3), 1964-1972 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration # USC 1800-1999 (Folder 2 of 3), 1964-1972 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration # USC 1800-1999 (Folder 3 of 3), 1964-1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 2000-2200 (Folder 1 of 2), 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 2000-2200 (Folder 2 of 2), 1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USS 4800-4900, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USS 4901-4999, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USS 5000-5099, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USS 5100-5199, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USS 5200- 5299, 1965-1968 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- U.S. Steel Arbitrations - U.S.S. 5300-6299. (Box 16)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USS 5300-5399, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USS 5400-5499, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USS 5600-5699, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USS 5500-5599, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USS 5600-5699, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USS 5700-5799 (Folder 1 of 2), 1966-1974 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Steel Corporation Board of Arbitration USS 5700-5799 (Folder 1 of 2), 1966-1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. Board of Arbitration USS 5800-5899, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Steel Corp. Board of Arbitration USS 5900-5999, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - 6099-6199, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 6200-6299, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- U.S. Steel Arbitrations - U.S.S. 6300-7099. (Box 17)
  - 6300-6399, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 6400-6499 (Folder 1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 6400-6499 (Folder 2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 6500-6599, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 6600-6699, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - 6800-6899, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 6900-6999 (Folder 1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 6900-6999 (Folder 2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - 6700-6799, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 7000-7099, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- U.S. Steel Arbitrations - U.S.S. 7100-8099. (Box 18)
  - 7100-7199, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 7200-7299, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 7300-7399, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 7400-7499, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - 7500-7599, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 7600-7699, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - 7700-7799, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - 7800-7899, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - 7900-7999, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - 8000-8099, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- U.S. Steel Arbitrations - U.S.S. 8100-9099. (Box 19)
  - 8100-8199, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 8200-8299, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 8300-8399 (Folder 1 of 2), 1971 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 8300-8399 (Folder 2 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 8400-8499, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - 8500-8599, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 8600-8699, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - 8700-8799, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - 8800-8899, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - 8900-8999, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - 9000-9099, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- U.S. Steel Arbitrations - U.S.S. 9100-10,199. (Box 20)
  - 9100-9199, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 9200-9299, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - 9300-9399, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 9400-9499, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 9500-9599, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - 9600-9699, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - 9700-9799, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - 9800-9899, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 9900-9999, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - 10,000-10,100, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 10,100-10,199, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- U.S. Steel Arbitrations - U.S.S. 10,200-10,999. (Box 21)
  - 10,200-10,299, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 10,300-10,399, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 10,400-10,499, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 10,500-10,599, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 10,800-10,899, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 10,600-10,699, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - 10,700-10,799, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - 10,900-10,999, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 11,000-11,100, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 9)